Emmanuel Bernal Velázquez

Frontend Developer

<u>LinkedIn</u> - <u>Behance</u> - <u>Github</u> - <u>Codepen</u> - <u>Email</u> Calimaya, Mexico

I'm a Frontend Developer and UI Designer specializing in web application development using JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, HTML, and CSS. I am passionate about programming and known for my creativity, punctuality, and responsibility. I excel in collaborative team environments and consistently demonstrate my commitment to achieving goals and overcoming challenges.

I have a personal project called "TheFrontdev," which is dedicated to sharing knowledge and continuous learning within the development community through <u>Instagram</u>.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer

Anzen Digital
Mexico City, Mexico.
November 2019 to date.

Activities:

- Develop web applications from scratch and proofs of concept with JavaScript using Angular, consuming REST APIs, working in conjunction with the UI/UX design team.
- Manage organizational Github account.
- Implement in some projects the continuous integration with AWS Amplify.
- Support banking application with Stencil.js, Angular, HTML, CSS as technology stack.
- Work under agile methodologies (SCRUM, Kanban).

Web Developer

Desarrollo Industrial RISORSE Toluca, Mexico. May2019 a Octuber 2019

Activities::

- Develop web applications with PHP using Laravel, JavaScript and MySQL.
- Develop desktop applications using C++ and SQL Server.

Web Developer

SatSys Calimaya, Mexico. Octubre 2018 a Abril de 2019

Actividades:

 Develop web applications with PHP using Symphony, Drupal CMS, JavaScript and MySQL.

Web Developer Jr

Bit Technologies Mexico Toluca, Mexico. July 2016 a June 2018

Actividades:

- Web application development with PHP using Laravel, JavaScript and MySQL.
- Customer support.

Education

Computer Systems Engineering

Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de Tianguistenco 2015 - 2018

Idiomas

- Español: nativo.
- Inglés: básico intermedio.

Certifications

Diseño UX/UI

CoderHouse Julio 2022

Marketing Digital: Community
 Manager & Publicidad

CoderHouse Marzo 2023

Technology Stack

- Angular
- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Git

- Figma
- CorelDraw
- MySQL
- PHP